Collection of Miscellaneous Philippine Pamphlets 5335
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Collection of Miscellaneous Philippine Pamphlets
1958-1963
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
University of the Philippines. Asian Labor Education Center
5335
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Pamphlets.
Miscellaneous pamphlets and other publications on labor issues in the Philippines.
8440889
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, November 15, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 11, 2019
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of miscellaneous pamphlets and other publications on labor issues in the Philippines.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Labor -- History -- Philippines; Labor -- Thailand; University of the Philippines. Asian Labor Education Center
8440889
- The ALEC Bulletin, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  University of the Philippines Asian Labor Education Center (ALEC)
  - Item 1: The ALEC Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By Fe Severino. v.8:no.3 (1962:Sep./Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: The ALEC Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By Fe Severino. v.8:no.4 (1962:Nov./Dec.). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: The ALEC Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    By Fe Severino. v.8:no.5 (1963:Jan./Feb.) 2 copies. Item is in English.
- ALEC publications, 1958-1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Asian Labor Education Center (ALEC)
  - Item 1: The Asian Labor Education Center Asian Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Asian Labor Education Center. A Study Program for Free Trade Union Leaders Offered by the University of the Philippines. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Philippine Program, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Asian Labor Education Center. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: On Labor-Management Relations, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Vincente G. Sinco; Gonzalo W. Gonzalez; Cicero D. Calderon; Ramon Magsaysay; Eleuterio Adevoso. Reprint Series no.1. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Asian Labor Education Center, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    By Cicero D. Calderon. Item is in English.
- History of Labor Federations in the Philippines, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: History of Labor Federations in the Philippines, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    By Asian Labor Education Center. March, 1961. Item is in English.
- Labor Monthly, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Labor Monthly: the Workers' Mirror, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    By Amado G. Inciong. v.2:no.11 (1962:Nov.). Item is in English.
- Labor in Thailand, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Labour in Thailand, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    By Yip Ching-Ping. From United Asia, v.12:no.3. Item is in English.
- National Development Company Annual Report, 1961-1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Annual Report of the General Manager, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    By National Development Company. For the fiscal year ended June 30, 1962. Item is in English.
- PTT-Asia Information Bulletin, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Postal, Telegraph and Telephone International (PTT)
  - Item 1: PTT-Asia Information Bulletin, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    By Postal, Telegraph and Telephone International (PTT). v.2:no.1 (1963:Jan.). Item is in English.
- Philippine Labor, 1962-1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Philippine Labor, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Department of Labor. v.1:no.6 (1962:Oct.). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Philippine Labor, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Department of Labor. v.1:no.7 (1962:Nov.). Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Philippine Labor, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    By Department of Labor. v.2:no.1 (1963:Jan.). Item is in English.
- 13th Resident Labor Training School, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: 13th Weekly, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Asian Labor Education Center. v.1:no.5 (1963:Feb.) Official Publication of the 13th Resident Labor Training School. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: 13th Resident Labor Training School List of Participants, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    By Asian Labor Education Center. January 14 - March 23, 1963. Item is in English.